<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="72">
    <author>Wopster</author>
    <version>2.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Manure System</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
            <![CDATA[The Manure System mod changes the whole gameplay around handling your manure application. Experience what it really means to pump liquids as a real farmer.
Use the fill arms to actually be able to pump from open sources like: manure containers, lagoons amd water sources.
Use a specialized dock arm in order to suck from a docking funnel, or simply use a suction hose.
With a suction hose you´re able to pump a liquid fill type from source to target. If applicable you could extend the liquid manure hose to reach larger ranges.
Pumping does not always happen at full efficiency, manure thickness decreases the pump capacity and also the length of hoses affects your pump time.

All vanilla vehicles are supported (and some have additional changes), for a full list please check the manual below.
For more information read <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/manureSystem/blob/master/README.md">the manual on my GitHub</a>.

Special thanks to VertexDezign and BM-Modding for providing awesome assets!

Slurry hose:
- Price: €150

Fertilizer hose:
- Price: €300

Changelog:
- Support for nested pump sources
- Fix issue with limited fill direction
- Allow for non strategy connector types

<a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/manureSystem/releases/tag/1.2.0.0">Full changelog here</a>
]]>
        </en>
        <de>
            <![CDATA[Das Gülle System verändert das ganze Spielerlebnis in der Handhabung der Gülle. Erfahre was es heisst, als echter Landwirt Gülle zu pumpen.
Nutze die Befüllarme um aus offenen Behältern wie Feldrandcontainern, Güllebecken und Wasserbecken zu pumpen.
Benutze einen speziellen Füllarm um von der Andockstation anzusaugen, oder einfach den Saugschlauch.
Mit dem Saugschlauch kannst Du Flüssigkeiten von einem in das andere Behältnis pumpen und diese einfach verlängern, um auch weitere Strecken zu überbrücken.
Das Pumpen geschieht nicht immer mit der gleichen Geschwindigkeit, da auch dickflüssige Gülle oder die Entfernung die Pumpenleistung beeinflussen.

Alle Standardfahrzeuge werden unterstützt ( und manche haben kleine Veränderungen bekommen ), für die komplette Liste bitte die Anleitung im Link hier drunter lesen.
Für weitere Informationen, lese dir die <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/manureSystem/blob/master/README.md">manual aus dem Github</a> durch.

Besonderen Dank an VertexDezign und BM-Modding für die Bereitstellung der tollen assets!

Gülleschlauch:
- Preis: 150 €

Düngerschlauch:
- Preis: 300 €

Changelog:
- Support for nested pump sources
- Fix issue with limited fill direction
- Allow for non strategy connector types

<a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/manureSystem/releases/tag/1.2.0.0">Full changelog here</a>
]]>
        </de>
        <fr>
            <![CDATA[Le mod Manure System change tout le gameplay autour de la gestion de votre installation de lisier. Découvrez ce que cela signifie vraiment de pomper des liquides en tant que véritable agriculteur.
Utilisez les bras de remplissage pour pouvoir pomper à partir de sources ouvertes telles que : les conteneurs de lisier, les bassins et les sources d'eau.
Utilisez un bras de remplissage spécialisé afin d'aspirer à partir du cône de raccordement, ou utilisez simplement un tuyau d'aspiration.
Avec un tuyau d'aspiration, vous pouvez pomper liquide de la source à la cible. Le cas échéant, vous pouvez allonger le tuyau d'aspiration pour atteindre de plus grandes distances.
Le pompage ne se fait pas toujours à pleine capacité, car le volume du lisier diminue la capacité de la pompe et la longueur des tuyaux influe également sur le temps de pompage.

Tous les véhicules de type vanilla sont pris en charge (et certains ont des modifications supplémentaires), pour une liste complète, veuillez consulter le manuel ci-dessous.
Pour plus d'informations, veuillez lire <a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/manureSystem/blob/master/README.md">le manuel sur mon GitHub</a>.

Un grand merci à VertexDezign et BM-Modding pour avoir fourni des fonctionnalités géniales !

Tuyau à lisier:
- Prix: €150

Tuyau à fertilisant:
- Prix: €300

Changelog:
- Support for nested pump sources
- Fix issue with limited fill direction
- Allow for non strategy connector types

<a href="https://github.com/stijnwop/manureSystem/releases/tag/1.2.0.0">Full changelog here</a>
]]>
        </fr>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon.png</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>

    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>

    <placeableSpecializations>
        <specialization name="manureSystemPlaceableSilo" className="ManureSystemPlaceableSilo" filename="src/placeables/specializations/ManureSystemPlaceableSilo.lua"/>
    </placeableSpecializations>

    <specializations>
        <specialization name="hose" className="Hose" filename="src/hose/Hose.lua"/>
        <specialization name="manureSystemPumpMotor" className="ManureSystemPumpMotor" filename="src/vehicles/ManureSystemPumpMotor.lua"/>
        <specialization name="manureSystemConnector" className="ManureSystemConnector" filename="src/vehicles/ManureSystemConnector.lua"/>
        <specialization name="manureSystemFillArm" className="ManureSystemFillArm" filename="src/vehicles/ManureSystemFillArm.lua"/>
        <specialization name="manureSystemFillArmReceiver" className="ManureSystemFillArmReceiver" filename="src/vehicles/ManureSystemFillArmReceiver.lua"/>
    </specializations>

    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="flexibleHose" className="Vehicle" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="baseMaterial"/>
            <specialization name="animatedVehicle"/>
            <specialization name="washable"/>
            <specialization name="wearable"/>
            <specialization name="foliageBending"/>
            <specialization name="tensionBeltObject"/>
            <specialization name="hose"/>
        </type>
    </vehicleTypes>

    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="resources/hoses/slurry/slurryHose.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="resources/hoses/slurry/slurryHose5m.xml"/>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="resources/hoses/fertilizer/fertilizerHose.xml"/>
    </storeItems>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="i18n/locale"/>

    <actions>
        <action name="MS_ATTACH_HOSE" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="MS_DETACH_HOSE" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="MS_TOGGLE_FLOW" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="MS_ACTIVATE_PUMP" axisType="HALF"/>
        <action name="MS_TOGGLE_PUMP_DIRECTION" axisType="HALF"/>
    </actions>

    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MS_ACTIVATE_PUMP">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_r"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_11"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MS_TOGGLE_PUMP_DIRECTION">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_z"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_5 BUTTON_17"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MS_ATTACH_HOSE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_RIGHT"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_1"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MS_DETACH_HOSE">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_LEFT"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_3"/>
        </actionBinding>
        <actionBinding action="MS_TOGGLE_FLOW">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="MOUSE_BUTTON_RIGHT"/>
            <binding device="GAMEPAD_DEFAULT" input="BUTTON_1"/>
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
